#### Contact

maita.galang@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mhaitzendriga0711 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

PHP

Codelgniter Web Framework ASP

# Maita Galang

Freelance Web Developer

Calabarzon

## Summary

Senior Web Developer with 12plus years of experience able to build web applications from the ground up – information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance. Proven ability in optimizing web applications functionalities that improve data retrieval and workflow efficiencies.

## Experience

Freelance

Freelance Web Developer February 2022 - Present (2 months)

Clarmil Manufacturing, Inc.
Senior Web Programmer
December 2008 - February 2022 (13 years 3 months)
Philippines

- Design and Develop ERP and MRP System
- Database and Server Maintenance Support for the ERP and MRP System
- Design and Develop POS and Financial System
- Design and Develop Ticketing System for Goldilocks Bakeshop Inc.
- Design and Develop Sales Order Reporting Tool for Goldilocks Bakeshop Inc.
- Design and Develop Sales Webform and Reports for Goldilocks Bakeshop Inc. for store use.
- Technical Support (PC/Printers/Network)

### Education

Pamantasan ng Cabuyao

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science (2003 - 2007)